const state =[
    {
        id:1,
        mark:"Бизнес аналитик",
        question:"Ответы (один вариант)",
        answer:"optionD",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet fchgyvjbk,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum  amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:2,
        numb:"тест-2",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionB",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet fhgcyjvk,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem  sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:3,
        numb:"тест-3",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionD",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet cgyjhvbk,m,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem  sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:4,
        numb:"тест-4",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionA",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet fyjghvbkn,",
        optionA:"Lorem amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:5,
        numb:"тест-5",
        answer:"optionC",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet fghvbjk,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:6,
        numb:"тест-6",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionB",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet tfhygjbknl,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum  amet," ,
        optionC:"ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:7,
        numb:"тест-7",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionD",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet gbcvhnbm,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lore amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:8,
        numb:"тест-8",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionC",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet xvcbnm,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:9,
        numb:"тест-9",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionA",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
    {
        id:10,
        numb:"тест-10",
        question:"lorem10",
        answer:"optionB",
        prompt:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet,",
        optionA:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionC:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionB:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
        optionD:"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet," ,
    },
]

export default state;